Every time Amanda Seales opens her
mouth,
she confirms why the [ __ ] no one likes
her.
Now, before we get into it, make sure
you like, share, comment, subscribe,
follow, do all the things. I'mma talk my
[ __ ] We're going to have a good time,
but let's get into it. So, Amanda Seales
decided to get her ass on her live
yesterday and basically say that
Cheyenne Bryant was brilliant when she
came on her show. She doesn't understand
what all of the vitriol is about and
that we basically, you know, gave Maya
Angelou, we called Maya Angelou a doctor
and she didn't have a real doctorate
degree. So, what's the big deal with
calling Cheyenne Bryant a doctor? And
she basically tried to make it seem as
if that she understands that doctorates
are important in certain fields, but it
seems as if Cheyenne Bryant hasn't
caused any harm. And that actually shows
that Amanda, you're not as smart as you
think you are. And that's what really
irritates me about you. You have
convinced so many people that you're so
intelligent that that they actually
think that you're smart. And every time
you open your mouth, you actually show
that you lack a lot of critical thinking
skills and that you say [ __ ] because you
need to get a check. Because at the end
of the day,
it's one or two things. Either you are
really smart and this is just a game
you're playing to cash a check because
you ain't getting no acting work or
you're really not as smart as you try to
portray and [snorts]
you literally made a statement on here
as you wish that people were as mad at
Kamala Harris as they are with Cheyenne
Bryant. And it's like you have this
thing for for Kamala Harris because
you literally just can't think outside
of yourself and you need something that
gives you a talking point on and it's a
way to be a contrarian
and get attention. So, let's break it
down. Maya Angelou
literally got her honorary doctorate
degrees, which she has multiple,
um because of the work that she did.
Because she was involved in the civil
rights movement and was a civil rights
leader. Because she worked on
presidential campaigns. Because her
works have been studied in a literary
sense. Her works have been studied in
college and high schools. She is
actually someone who has had a framework
of things that have been analyzed by
literature experts. She's received
governmental awards. She's was a
Pulitzer Prize nominee, a Tony Award
nominee. She received the Presidential
Medal of Freedom. I mean, what are we
talking about? How are you comparing the
two?
She was the first black woman depicted
on a quarter. And it wasn't because her
work was fake. She was able to back up
her literature works. This woman has
over 50 honorary degrees. I'mma post it
in right here. So, you're going to tell
me that this list can equal to Cheyenne
Bryant's list? When
Make it make sense. Where Cheyenne
Bryant's honorary degree
was from Harvest Christian, the same
school that just gave Chris Brown one.
The unaccredited religious organization
that has zero accreditation. That's
basically a school that you can get a
tax deduction for donating there.
That's where she got her degree from.
So, you literally twisted your mouth to
put them in the same category when this
woman got her freaking honorary degree
from this fake ass [ __ ] school.
And Maya Angelou has more than 50
honorary degrees based on all of her
work.
Maya did the work for us to call her Dr.
Angelou. Even though it was honorary
degrees, she's got the years of work to
back it up.
This chick has not one honorary
doctorate from
a actual school.
A real school. Dr. Maya Angelou's Smith
College,
Mount Holyoke, and Mills College, all
actual real schools.
You just wanted to get your likes up and
get your views up for a check.
You do this every few months. You come
up with some [ __ ] just to get a
[ __ ] check because your ass ain't
getting no acting jobs.
And you know that you've pretty much
squandered your whole acting career. So,
you got to get on here and do some
[ __ ] to get some clicks and views to
get that YouTube check.
You're ridiculous and I really, really
wish people would stop listening to your
ass.